var questionArray = [
{question:"let's meet ____ the museum.",
a:"in",
b:"at",
c:"on",
d:"to",
answer:"at",
},
{question:"he bought ____ new car yesterday.",
a:"a",
b:"an",
c:"these",
d:"this",
answer:"a"
},
{question:"we went ____ a concert yesterday morning.",
a:"in",
b:"at",
c:"on",
d:"to",
answer:"to"
},
{question:"I ____ the bus to work this morning.",
a:"took",
b:"take",
c:"taken",
d:"taked",
answer:"took"
},
{question:"how ____ students attend the school today?",
a:"much",
b:"many",
c:"a",
d:"nothing",
answer:"many",
},
{question:"Jaret has ____ money in the bank.",
a:"a",
b:"any",
c:"some",
d:"nothing",
answer:"some",
},
{question:"would you like ____ cream in your coffee?",
a:"any",
b:"some",
c:"a",
d:"nothing",
answer:"some",
},
{question:"____ book was written by Jane Anders.",
a:"an",
b:"any",
c:"this",
d:"these",
answer:"this",
},
{question:"how ____ bread do we have in the kitchen?",
a:"many",
b:"much",
c:"a",
d:"nothing",
answer:"much",
},
{question:"Now,There ____ milk in the refrigerator.",
a:"is",
b:"are",
c:"was",
d:"nothing",
answer:"is",
},
{question:"I have ____ friends in America.",
a:"a little",
b:"a few",
c:"any",
d:"nothing",
answer:"a few",
},
{question:"Many like to eat ____ chicken for dinner.",
a:"some",
b:"any",
c:"the",
d:"nothing",
answer:"some",
},
{question:"There is ____ ice-cream.",
a:"many",
b:"a lot of",
c:"a",
d:"nothing",
answer:"a lot of",
},
{question:"Eating ____ chocolate is unhealthy.",
a:"many",
b:"a lot of",
c:"a",
d:"nothing",
answer:"a lot of",
},
{question:"We don't drink ____ orange juice.",
a:"many",
b:"much",
c:"a lot of",
d:"nothing",
answer:"much",
}]



















